Guide to the TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
- A-Team #1: Defense Against Terror {Plot-It-Yourself} by William Rotsler Wanderer 49608 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 44)
- A-Team #2: The Danger Maze [Plot-It-Yourself] by William Rotsler Wanderer 52761 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 44)
- Annie Oakley in Danger at Diablo by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1540 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 44)
- Annie Oakley in the Ghost Town Secret by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1538 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 44)
- Annie Oakley in Double Trouble by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1538 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 44)
- Bat Masterson by Wayne C. Lee Whitman 1550 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 44)
- The Beverly Hillbillies: The Saga of Wildcat Creek by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1572 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 44)
- Bewitched: The Opposite Uncle by William Johnston Whitman 1572 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 44)
- The Big Valley by Charles Heckelmann Whitman 1569 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 44)
- Bonanza: Killer Lion by Steve Frazee Whitman 1568 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 44)
- Bonanza: Heroes of the Wild West by B.L. Bonham, ed. Whitman 1569 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 45)
- Bonanza: Treachery Trail by Harry Whittington Whitman 1571 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 45)
- Cheyenne and the Lost Gold of Lion Park by Steve Frazee Whitman 1587 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 45)
- Circus Boy: Under the Big Top by Dorothea J. Snow Whitman 1549 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 45)
- Circus Boy: War on Wheels by Dorothea J. Snow Whitman 1578 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 45)
- Combat: The Counterattack by Franklin M. Davis, Jr. Whitman 1520 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 45)
- Dr. Kildare: Assigned to Trouble by Robert C. Ackworth Whitman 1547 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 45)
- Dr. Kildare: The Magic Key by William Johnston Whitman 1519 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 45)
- Dragnet: Case histories from the popular television series by Richard Deming Whitman 1527 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 45)
- Dragnet: Case histories from the popular television series by Richard Deming Whitman 1510 ca. 1957,70 (unsp: 1970) (Box 45)
- F Troop: The Great Indian Uprising by William Johnston Whitman 1544 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 46)
- Family Affair: Buffy Finds a Star by Gladys Baker Bond Whitman 1567 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 46)
- Father Murphy's Promises by Larry Weinberg Random House 85318 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 46)
- Flip Wilson Close-Up by James A. Hudson Scholastic Book Services TX1933 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 46)
- Flip by James A. Hudson Scholastic Book Services TX2030 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 46)
- "flipper": The Mystery of the Black Schooner by Richard Hardwick Whitman 2324 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 46)
- Fury and the Lone Pine Mystery by William Fenton Whitman 1537 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 46)
- Fury and the Mystery at Trappers' Hole by Troy Nesbit [Franklin Folsom] Whitman 1557 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 46)
- Garrison's Gorillas and the Fear Formula by Jack Pearl Whitman 1548 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 46)
- Gene Autry and the Badmen of Broken Arrow by Snowden Miller Whitman 2355 ca. 1951 (1st) (Box 46)
- Gene Autry and the Big Valley Crab by W.H. Hutchinson Whitman 2302 ca. 1952 (1st) (Box 46)
- Gene Autry and the Golden Stallion by Cole Fannin Whitman 1511 ca. 1954 (1st) (Box 46)
- Gene Autry and the Ghost Riders by Lewis B. Patten Whitman 1510 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 47)
- Gene Autry and Arapaho War Drums by Lewis B. Patten Whitman 1512 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 47)
- Gilligan's Island by William Johnston Whitman 1566 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 47)
- Good Times: Jimmie Walker: The Dyn-O-Mite Kid by Joel H. Cohen Scholastic Book Services TX3442 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 47)
- Good Times: Jimmie Walker: The Dyn-O-Mite Kid by Joel H. Cohen Scholastic Book Services TX3442 ca. 1976 (1st) (2nd Copy) (Box 47)
- The Green Hornet: The Case of the Disappearing Doctor by Brandon Keith Whitman 1570 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 47)
- Gun Law: The Mystery of Jan Gant's Treasure by Robert Turner World Distributors (Box 47)
- Gunsmoke by Robert Turner Whitman 1587 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 47)
- Gunsmoke: Showdown on Front Street by Paul S. Newman Whitman 1520 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 47)
- Hardy Boys Detective Logic Puzzles by Wayne Williams Tempo 14510 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 47)
- Nancy Drew and The Hardy Boys by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services TX4103 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 47)
- The Hardy Boys and Nancy Drew by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services TX4496 ca. 1977,78 (2nd: 1978) (Box 47)
- Have Gun, Will Travel by Barlow Meyers Whitman 1568 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 47)
- Hawaii Five-O: Top Secret by Robert Sidney Bowen Whitman 1511 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 48)
- Hawaii Five-O: The Octopus Caper by Leo R. Ellis Whitman 1553 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 48)
- Laugh With Lucy: The Story of Lucille Ball by Joel H. Cohen Scholastic Book Services TX2544 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 48)
- The High Chaparral: Apache Way by Steve Frazee Whitman 1519 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 48)
- I Spy: Message From Moscow by Brandon Keith Whitman 1542 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 48)
- Robert Culp & Bill Cosby by Ed Goodgold Grosset & Dunlap 1097 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 48)
- Cool Cos: The Story of Bill Cosby by Joel H. Cohen Scholastic Book Services TX1388 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 48)
- Invaders: Dam of Death by Jack Pearl Whitman 1545 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 48)
- Ironside: The Picture Frame Frame-Up by William Johnston Whitman 1521 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 48)
- Joanie Loves Chachi #1: Secrets by William Rotsler Wanderer 46010 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 48)
- Land of the Giants: Flight of Fear by Carl Henry Rathjen Whitman 1516 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 48)
- Lassie and the Mystery at Blackberry Bog by Dorothea J. Snow Whitman 1536 ca. 1956 (1st) (Box 48)
- Lassie and the Secret Summer by Dorothea J. Snow Whitman 1589 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 48)
- Lassie and the Secret Summer by Dorothea J. Snow Whitman 1589 ca. 1958 (1st) (Alternate Copy) (Box 48)
- Lassie and the Secret Summer by Dorothea J. Snow Whitman 1500 ca. 1958 (unsp: 1964) (Box 49)
- Lassie: Forbidden Valley by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1508 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 49)
- Lassie: Treasure Hunter by Charles S. Strong Whitman 1552 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 49)
- Lassie: The Wild Mountain Trail by I.G. Edmonds Whitman 1513 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 49)
- Lassie: The Mystery of Bristlecone Pine by Steve Frazee Whitman 1505 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 49)
- Lassie: The Secret of Smelters' Cave by Steve Frazee Whitman 1514 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 49)
- Lassie: Lost in Snow by Steve Frazee Whitman 1504 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 49)
- Lassie: Trouble at Panter's Lake by Steve Frazee Whitman 1515 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 49)
- The Lennon Sisters: The Secret of Holiday Island by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1544 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 49)
- Janet Lennon: Adventure at Two Rivers by Barlow Meyers Whitman 1536 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 49)
- Janet Lennon at Camp Calamity by Barlow Meyers Whitman 1539 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 49)
- Janet Lennon and the Angels by Barlow Meyers Whitman 1583 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 50)
- Leave it to Beaver by Cole Fannin Whitman 1526 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 50)
- The Love Boat #1: Voyage of Love [Plot-It-Yourself] by William Rotsler Wanderer 49802 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 50)
- Lucy and the Madcap Mystery by Cole Fannin Whitman 1505 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 50)
- Magnum, P.I. #1: Maui Mystery [Plot-It-Yourself] by William Rotsler Wanderer 49607 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 50)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. and the Affair of the Gentle Saboteur by Brandon Keith Whitman 1541 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 50)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. and the Affair of the Gunrunners' Gold by Brandon Keith Whitman 1543 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 50)
- Maverick by Charles L. Coombs Whitman 1566 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 50)
- Walt Disney's Spin and Marty: Trouble at Triple-R by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1577 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 50)
- Walt Disney's Annette: Sierra Summer by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1585 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 50)
- Walt Disney's Annette: The Desert Inn Mystery by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1546 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 50)
- Walt Disney's Annette and the Mystery of Moonstone Bay by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1537 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 50)
- Walt Disney's Annette and the Mystery of Smugglers' Cove by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1574 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 51)
- Walt Disney's Annette: Mystery at Medicine Wheel by Barlow Meyers Whitman 1512 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 51)
- Mission Impossible: The Priceless Particle by Talmage Powell Whitman 1515 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 51)
- Mission Impossible: The Money Explosion by Talmage Powell Whitman 1512 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 51)
- Mr. Merlin Episod 1 by William Rotsler Wanderer 44479 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 51)
- Mr. Merlin Episode 2 by William Rotsler Wanderer 44480 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 51)
- The Mod Squad: Assignment: The Arranger by Richard Deming Whitman 1538 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 51)
- The Mod Squad: Assignment: The Hideout by Richard Deming Whitman 1517 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 51)
- The Monkees in Who's Got the Button? by William Johnston Whitman 1539 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 51)
- The Mork & Mindy Story by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services 05756 ca. 1979 (Box 51)
- The Mork & Mindy Story by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services TX4757 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 51)
- The Munsters and the Great Camera Caper by William Johnston Whitman 1510 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 51)
- The Munsters: The Last Resort by William Johnston Whitman 1567 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 51)
- Meet David Cassidy by James A. Hudson Scholastic Book Services TX2123 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 51)
- Meet David Cassidy by James A. Hudson Scholastic Book Services TX2123 ca. 1972 (1st) (2nd Copy) (Box 51)
- Patty Duke and Mystery Mansion by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1514 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 52)
- Patty Duke and the Adventure of the Chinese Junk by Doris Schroeder Whitman 2334 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 52)
- The Rat Patrol: The Iron Monster Raid by I.G. Edmonds Whitman 1547 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 52)
- The Real McCoys and Danger at the Ranch by Cole Fannin Whitman 1557 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 52)
- The Rebel by H.A. De Rosso Whitman 1548 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 52)
- The Restless Gun by Barlow Meyers Whitman 1559 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 52)
- The Rifleman by Cole Fannin Whitman 1569 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 52)
- Rin Tin Tin's Rinty by Julie Campbell Whitman 1542 ca. 1954 (1st) (Box 52)
- Rin Tin Tin and the Ghost Wagon Train by Cole Fannin Whitman 1579 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 52)
- Rin Tin Tin and Call to Danger by Doris Schroeder Whitman 1539 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 53)
- Ripcord by D.S. Halacy, Jr. Whitman 1522 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 53)
- Roy Rogers and the Rimrod Renegades by Snowden Miller Whitman 2305 ca. 1952 (1st) (Box 53)
- Roy Rogers and the Enchanted Canyon by Jim Rivers Whitman 1502 ca. 1954 (1st) (Box 53)
- Roy Rogers on the Trail of the Zeroes by Packer Elton Whitman 2361 ca. 1954 (1st) (Box 53)
- Roy Rogers and The Brasada Bandits by Cole Fannin Whitman 1500 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 53)
- Roy Rogers: King of the Cowboys by Cole Fannin Whitman 1503 ca. 1956 (1st) (Box 53)
- Roy Rogers and Dale Evans in River of Pearl by Cole Fannin Whitman 1504 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 53)
- Dale Evans and Danger in Crooked Canyon by Helen Hale [Lucile Burnett Mulcahy] Whitman 1506 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 54)
- Sea Hunt by Cole Fannin Whitman 1541 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 54)
- Star Trek: Mission to Horatius by Mack Reynolds Whitman 1549 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 54)
- Wells Fargo and Danger Station by Sam Allison [Noel Loomis] Whitman 1588 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 54)
- Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea by Raymond F. Jones Whitman 1517 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 54)
- Wagon Train by Troy Nesbit Whitman 1567 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 54)
- Legends of Davy Crockett by Ardis Edwards Burton Whitman 1619 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 54)
- The Waltons #1: The Bird Dog by Dion Henderson Whitman 1516 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 54)
- The Waltons #2: The Puzzle by Carl Henry Rathjen Whitman 1576 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 54)
- The Waltons #3: The Penny Sale by Gladys Baker Bond Whitman 1599 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 54)
- The Waltons #4: The Treasures by Carl Henry Rathjen Whitman 1580 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 54)
- The Waltons #5: Up She Rises! by Gladys Baker Bond Whitman 1539 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 54)
- The Waltons #6: The Accident by Virginia McDonnell Whitman 1510 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 55)
- Wyatt Earp by Philip Ketchum Whitman 1548 ca. 1956 (1st) (Box 55)
- Walt Disney's Zorro by Steve Frazee Whitman 1535 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 55)